<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authors on TJNU-iOS-Club</title><link>/authors/</link><description>Recent content in Authors on TJNU-iOS-Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>TJNU-iOS-Club &amp;copy; {year}</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/authors/liushuxuan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/liushuxuan/</guid><description>I am a undergaduate Software Engineeering student in Tianjin Normal University.
I participated in the tenth section of China University Student Service Outsourcing Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition and Tianjin Normal University School-level Daiso Project.
Currently working on iOS development.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/niujiahui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/niujiahui/</guid><description>I am a 2019 undergraduate of software engineering at Tianjin Normal University. As a project member, I participated in the 2020 school-level innovation and entrepreneurship project.
My main interest is in human-computer interaction and algorithm research.
Vue.js and other front-end technologies have been studied, and I am currently studying back-end development technologies, such as java.
More info about me: https://jeffniu.top/</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/wangpenghao/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/wangpenghao/</guid><description>I am a sophomore major in software engineering at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I am a core member of iOS Club. Besides, I am a key member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab at my TJNU, advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/yangjin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/yangjin/</guid><description>Now I am studying software engineering at Tianjin Normal University. I have a strong interest in computer programming languages ​​and machine learning models, and like to brainstorm and organize my own knowledge system.
Competition experience: As a project member, I participated in the tenth section of China University Student Service Outsourcing Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition. As the project leader, I established Tianjin Normal University School-level Daiso Project.
Research direction: The main research direction at present is machine learning and computer networks.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/zhixianzhang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/zhixianzhang/</guid><description>I am a 2019 undergraduate in software engineering at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I have mastered C++, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and other programming languages. I have a good development foundation in basic courses such as CS61B spring2018 and MIT6.004 spring2020. I have participated in 2020. National University IOT Design Competition(Huawei), 2020 China College Student Computer Design Competition, 2020 American College Student Mathematical Modeling Competition, 2020 College Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition, The 6th China College Students&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;Internet Plus&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition, and served as the team technical leader, Accumulated technology stacks such as Docker, KubeEdge, and VUE.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/jiaojinlong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/jiaojinlong/</guid><description>I am an undergraduate software engineering student at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I am a core member of iOS Club and I have attended Apple Summer Camp Nanjing of China, 2018. Additionaly, I am a key member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab from Center for Affective Intelligence International Studies at my TJNU, advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao.
Currently participating in the project development of “support theory and innovation model of healthy pension cross-border service”.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/zhaoyiqin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/zhaoyiqin/</guid><description>I am a senior undergaduate Software Engineeering student at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I am also a key member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao at TJNU. I love both research and industrial, I had a wonderful internship experience at Baidu DuerOS department major in web development.
My research at TJNU is focused on applied machine learning and affective computing. If you are interested, checkout my selected projects and publications at below.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/admin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/admin/</guid><description>We are the iOS club of Tianjin Normal University, a student community strongly supported by Apple and the school of software of Tianjin Normal University.We are committed to building an iOS developer association that promotes learning and practice outside the classroom, building a team and creating the first iOS app in our life.
It is just a basic operation to learn about iOS development, UI design, video cre-ation and other related technologies here.</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/fanjiawen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/fanjiawen/</guid><description>I am a 2018 undergraduate in software engineering at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I participated in the 2019 ShangHai Winter Camp as a core member of the TJNU iOS Club.
Currently serving as the president of the 2020 TJNU iOS Club.
Awards: 2019 National University Computer Ability Challenge Big Data Algorithm Competition National Second Prize (Top5%) The second prize of the 2020 China University Computer Design Competition Tianjin Division The third prize of the Tianjin Division of the China &amp;ldquo;Internet +&amp;rdquo; Contest in 2020 2020 National Project &amp;ldquo;Ben Mo Ying Xia&amp;rdquo; of China University Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Project</description></item><item><title/><link>/authors/liujingyu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/liujingyu/</guid><description>A 2016 undergraduate student major in Computer Science and Technology at Tianjin Normal University. The main research direction: iOS development.
TJNU iOS Club Technical Lecturer.
Independent developer of iOS App &amp;ldquo;Get Social&amp;rdquo;.
Currently participating in the development of the &amp;ldquo;Online Habit Game&amp;rdquo; experimental project at the University of Southern California.
More information about me: https://fix.moe.</description></item></channel></rss>